Boston Streets Collection MS102
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Boston City Directories, 1845 -- 1925; 1845 -- 1960; MS102.002; 2703 Digital Object(s)
  - 1925, MS102.002.011; 572 Digital Object(s)
    - Advertisements. State House - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00124; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. State House - Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00125; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00126; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00127; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00128; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00129; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00130; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00131; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00132; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00133; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Tremont Street - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00134; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00135; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Public Gardens - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00136; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Public Gardens - Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00137; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00138; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00139; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00140; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00141; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Harvard Club - 374 Commonwealth Avenue, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00142; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Harvard Club - 374 Commonwealth Avenue in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00143; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Sexton Can Co. Colonial Can Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00144; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Sexton Can Co. Colonial Can Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00145; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00146; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00147; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Harvard Gate - Cambridge, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00148; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Harvard Gate - Cambridge in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00149; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00150; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00151; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Linder & Meyer. Merrimac Chemical Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00152; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Linder & Meyer. Merrimac Chemical Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00153; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. State House - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00154; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00155; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00156; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Nelson H. Brown Clocks. E. Howard Clock Company, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00157; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Nelson H. Brown Clocks. E. Howard Clock Company in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00158; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Commonwealth Pier - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00159; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Commonwealth Pier - Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00160; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00161; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Burton-Furber Coal Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00162; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Burton-Furber Coal Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Metropolitan Coal Company, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00163; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Metropolitan Coal Company in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00164; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00165; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00166; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00167; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00168; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Adams Pond Company. Grid Flat Slab Corporation, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00169; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Adams Pond Company. Grid Flat Slab Corporation in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - William T. Reed Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00170; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of William T. Reed Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Simpson Bros. Corporation, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00171; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Simpson Bros. Corporation in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Simpson Bros. Corporation, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00172; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - C.A. Dodge Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00173; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of C.A. Dodge Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - W.A. Murtfeldt Company, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00174; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of W.A. Murtfeldt Company in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - S.C. Sperry Co., Inc., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00175; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of S.C. Sperry Co., Inc. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - John Cavanagh & Son Building Moving Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00176; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of John Cavanagh & Son Building Moving Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Warren Brothers Company. D.M. Biggs & Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00177; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Warren Brothers Company. D.M. Biggs & Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00178; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00179; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00180; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00181; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00182; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00183; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00184; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Blake House - Dorchester, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00185; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Blake House - Dorchester in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00186; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00187; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00188; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00189; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00190; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00191; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00192; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00193; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Rockport Granite Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00194; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Rockport Granite Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Portland Stone Ware Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00195; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Portland Stone Ware Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Waldo Bros. and Bond Company, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00196; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Waldo Bros. and Bond Company in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Sampson & Murdock Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00197
      Page image of Sampson & Murdock Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00198; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00199; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00200; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00201; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00202; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Sampson & Murdock Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00203
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00204; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Geo H. Sampson Co. Dyar Sales and Machinery Company, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00205; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Geo H. Sampson Co. Dyar Sales and Machinery Company in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Perrin, Seamans & Co. Walter W. Field & Son, Inc., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00206; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Perrin, Seamans & Co. Walter W. Field & Son, Inc. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00207; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Dahlquist Manufacturing Co. Boston Copper Works Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00208; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Dahlquist Manufacturing Co. Boston Copper Works Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Gerstein Bros. & Cooper. E.B. Badger & Sons Company, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00209; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Gerstein Bros. & Cooper. E.B. Badger & Sons Company in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00210; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Louisburg Square - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00211; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Louisburg Square - Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00212; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00213; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00214; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00215; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00216; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00217; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00218; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - A.W.D. Secret Service Bureau. Old North Church - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00219; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of A.W.D. Secret Service Bureau. Old North Church - Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - James R. Wood Detective Agency, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00220; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of James R. Wood Detective Agency in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - James R. Wood Detective Agency, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00221; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00222; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00223; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00224; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00225; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. King's Chapel - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00226; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. King's Chapel - Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Brown Durrell Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00227; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Brown Durrell Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00228; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00229; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Custom House, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00230; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Custom House in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00231; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00232; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00233; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00234; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00235; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00236; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00237; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Tremont Street - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00238; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Gifford-Wood Material Handling Equipment, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00239; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Gifford-Wood Material Handling Equipment in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements. State House - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00240; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - The MacDonald Elevator Company. Harvard Medical Schools, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00241; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of The MacDonald Elevator Company. Harvard Medical Schools in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Geo T. McLauthlin Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00242; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Geo T. McLauthlin Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00243; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Armory for Mounted Troops - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00244; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Armory for Mounted Troops - Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00245; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00246; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Spraco Paint Spraying Equipment, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00247; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Spraco Paint Spraying Equipment in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00248; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00249; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00250; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00251; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00252; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00253; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Walter H. Moreton Corp., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00254; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Walter H. Moreton Corp. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00255; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - H.C. Whitcomb Co. FitzGerald Engraving Company, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00256; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of H.C. Whitcomb Co. FitzGerald Engraving Company in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - American Engraving Co. Suffolk Engraving & Electrotyping Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00257; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of American Engraving Co. Suffolk Engraving & Electrotyping Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00258; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00259; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Thomas J. Grey Co. R. & J. Farquhar Company, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00260; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Thomas J. Grey Co. R. & J. Farquhar Company in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00261; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00262; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00263; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00264; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Seeley & Lawson. T Wharf and Custom House - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00265; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Seeley & Lawson. T Wharf and Custom House - Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00266; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00267; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Boston Floor Co., Ltd. Wm. J. Day & Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00268; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Boston Floor Co., Ltd. Wm. J. Day & Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00269; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00270; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00271; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00272; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00273; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00274; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00275; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00276; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00277; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Kakas Bros., Inc., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00278; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Kakas Bros., Inc. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - W. Davidson. First Parish in Dorchester, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00279; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of W. Davidson. First Parish in Dorchester in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00280; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00281; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Boston Gear Works Sales Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00282; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Boston Gear Works Sales Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00283; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. T Wharf, Boston, Mass., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00284; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Boston Plate & Window Glass Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00285; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Boston Plate & Window Glass Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements. South Boston Yacht Club - South Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00286; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. South Boston Yacht Club - South Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Standard Plate Glass Company, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00287; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Standard Plate Glass Company in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00288; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00289; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements. Brae Burn Club - West Newton, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00290; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Brae Burn Club - West Newton in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00291; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00292; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Chandler & Farquhar Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00293; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Chandler & Farquhar Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - A.J. Wilkinson & Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00294; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of A.J. Wilkinson & Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00295; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00296; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00297; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00298; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00299; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00300; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00301; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00302; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - John Hancock House - Boston, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00303; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of John Hancock House - Boston in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements. Public Garden, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00304; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements. Public Garden in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00305; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Cyrus Brewer & Co., 1925; MS102.002.011.DO.00306; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Cyrus Brewer & Co. in The Boston directory for the year commencing August 1, 1925 Institute of Museum and Library Services